<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>heap on Nguyen Hoang Trung</title>
    <link>https://trungnguyen1909.github.io/blog/tags/heap/</link>
    <description>Recent content in heap on Nguyen Hoang Trung</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 14:35:17 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://trungnguyen1909.github.io/blog/tags/heap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AceBear Security Contest House-of-loop</title>
      <link>https://trungnguyen1909.github.io/blog/post/AceBear2019/house_of_loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 14:35:17 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://trungnguyen1909.github.io/blog/post/AceBear2019/house_of_loop/</guid>
      <description>House-of-loop Hi everyone, this is the writeup for the challenge House-of-loop in the AceBear Security Contest 2019
Description We are given a stripped ELF x64 binary which can be interacted with, our task is to get remote code execution(RCE).
The binary presents us 3 options: Create, View and Delete a note.
When creating a note, we have 3 fields: Title, Private, and Description.
We have the limits on Title, Private field length but with Description, we can use as much as we specified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RITSEC18 Yet another HR Management Framework</title>
      <link>https://trungnguyen1909.github.io/blog/post/RITSEC-2018/Yet-another-HR-Management-Framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 21:30:28 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://trungnguyen1909.github.io/blog/post/RITSEC-2018/Yet-another-HR-Management-Framework/</guid>
      <description>By judging the program&amp;rsquo;s interface, we know that it was a heap challenge.
Spent quite a lot of time reversing it, I figured it out that it malloc a few bytes for the person struct on the heap, then the name will be malloc with the size entered and that address will be put in the person struct.
The person struct also has a function pointer which is set to the printPerson function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>matesCTF notebook</title>
      <link>https://trungnguyen1909.github.io/blog/post/matesctf/notebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 11:56:50 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://trungnguyen1909.github.io/blog/post/matesctf/notebook/</guid>
      <description>Notebook Bài này mình pwn được sau khi được tiền bối Đào Xuân Nghĩa thông não sau giờ.
Đây là 1 bài Heap overflow.
checksec:
[*] &#39;/root/matesctf/notebook&#39; Arch: amd64-64-little RELRO: Partial RELRO Stack: No canary found NX: NX enabled PIE: No PIE (0x400000) Có 2 loại note (bình thường: 1000bytes. Lớn: 2000bytes)
Các notes được lưu ở dạng double linked-list. 16 bytes đầu của mỗi note sẽ lưu note tiếp theo(FD) và note trước (BK)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>